<resources>
    <string name="app_name"> Chary </string>

    <string name="intro_text"> Save Your DAMN Life! </string>

    <string name="default_msg"> I\'M IN DANGER! </string>
    <string name="widget_button_text">SEND SOS</string>

    <string name="emg_contacts_text"> Long tap on an emergency contact to delete it. </string>
    <string name="info_tag">Click this icon above to know how to use the app.</string>
    <string name="settings_tag">Click this icon to go to the App\'s Settings.</string>
    <string name="sos_tag">Click this icon below to send SOS message.</string>
    <string name="Chary_tag">Chary</string>
    <string name="Chary_tagline">Never Walk Alone..</string>

    <string name="info">

    <b> The aim of this Android SOS application is to let a group of people know that a person is in a dangerous situation so that those people can rescue the person in danger.\n
        \n ***************************** </b> \n
       \n So this is how the app works:  \n

\n 1.This android app will inform those people by sending an SMS containing a piece of text, which may be default or custom,
        along with the user’s current location in the form of a URL link which will open up in Google Map.

\n \n 2.The SOS SMS can be triggered in the following three ways...

\n \n \t\t a)By pressing the POWER BUTTON 4 times continuously.
\n \n \t\t b)From the App Widget present on the home screen.
\n \n \t\t c)And from within the app itself.
        \n \n 3.The SOS app provides the user to add maximum three emergency contacts numbers from 	his/hers contact list.
        And the app will send SOS SMS to only those contacts. The user can also change the emergency contacts.


	\n \n 4.   The app has a default SOS text such as “I AM IN DANGER”, moreover the user can also add his/her own custom text.


	\n \n 5.   When the SOS SMS is triggered by pressing the POWER BUTTON, the app will inform the user that SMS has been sent out successfully by providing a
        haptic feedback (means vibrating the phone for 1000 ms).

         \n \n
        *****************************
        \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t

        \n \n
</string>


    <string name="into_land">
        <b> The aim of this Android SOS application is to let a group of people know that a person
            is in a dangerous situation so that those people can rescue the person in danger.
        </b>
    </string>

    <string name="inst_land">
        So this is how the app works:\n

\n 1.This android app will inform those people by sending an SMS containing a piece of text, which may be default or custom,
        along with the user’s current location in the form of a URL link which will open up in Google Map.

\n \n 2.The SOS SMS can be triggered in the following three ways...

\n \n \t\t a)By pressing the POWER BUTTON 4 times continuously.
\n \n \t\t b)From the App Widget present on the home screen.
\n \n \t\t c)And from within the app itself.
        \n \n 3.The SOS app provides the user to add maximum three emergency contacts numbers from 	his/hers contact list.
        And the app will send SOS SMS to only those contacts. The user can also change the emergency contacts.


	\n \n 4.   The app has a default SOS text such as “I AM IN DANGER”, moreover the user can also add his/her own custom text.


	\n \n 5.   When the SOS SMS is triggered by pressing the POWER BUTTON, the app will inform the user that SMS has been sent out successfully by providing a
        haptic feedback (means vibrating the phone for 1000 ms).

         \n \n
    </string>


</resources>
